<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Authors on JFrog Engineering</title>
    <link>http://engineering.jfrog.com/authors/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Authors on JFrog Engineering</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    
	<atom:link href="http://engineering.jfrog.com/authors/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Baruch Sadogursky</title>
      <link>http://engineering.jfrog.com/authors/baruch-sadogursky/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://engineering.jfrog.com/authors/baruch-sadogursky/</guid>
      <description>Baruch Sadogursky (a.k.a JBaruch) is the Head of Developer Relations and a Developer Advocate at JFrog. His passion is speaking about technology. Well, speaking in general, but doing it about technology makes him look smart, and 17 years of hi-tech experience sure helps.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Eyal Ben Moshe</title>
      <link>http://engineering.jfrog.com/authors/eyal-ben-moshe/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://engineering.jfrog.com/authors/eyal-ben-moshe/</guid>
      <description>Eyal has been leading the Eco-System team at JFrog for the past 4 years. They have been developing and maintaining innovative open source projects, all under the domain of CI/CD and DevOps automation solutions: the Jenkins Artifactory Plugin and JFrog CLI.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>JFrog</title>
      <link>http://engineering.jfrog.com/authors/jfrog/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://engineering.jfrog.com/authors/jfrog/</guid>
      <description>We set out on our journey in 2008, with the mission to transform the way enterprises manage and release software updates. We’ve realized that the world has changed, and users now expect their software to update continuously, non-intrusively and without them even knowing, this hyper connected world experience can be enabled by automation and an end-to-end solution for software artifacts only.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Leon Stigter</title>
      <link>http://engineering.jfrog.com/authors/leon-stigter/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://engineering.jfrog.com/authors/leon-stigter/</guid>
      <description>Leon is a Developer Advocate at JFrog where his focus is on helping developers get the most out of their DevOps tools with the end goal of enabling those developers to achieve the Liquid Software vision.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Pearlynn Dang</title>
      <link>http://engineering.jfrog.com/authors/pearlynn-dang/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://engineering.jfrog.com/authors/pearlynn-dang/</guid>
      <description>Pearlynn is a Community Engagement Manager with JFrog, working with the community of JFrog customers and users for the last two years. She&amp;rsquo;s active on conferences, meetups and online to help the developers do their job better using DevOps proccesses, culture and tools.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>